limas goddess of famine during your
opponent's turn opponent workers cannot
build on spaces neighboring your workers
unless building a dome to create a
complete tower Lee missus hunger follows
her workers around like a dark arm
creating a void zone where only limas
can build each turn use limas to block
your opponent's attempts to create a
high enough tower to climb up just by
being in the area if you can prevent
them from building at all they also lose
the game you'll have to rely on your own
builds to move yourself up in the city
since your opponent won't be able to
build a step up for you remember they
can still finish towers you're trying to
get to the top o with domes so don't
starve them too much or they'll never
leave you alone to sneak in your victory
[Music]