Gaea goddess of the earth when a worker
build a dome if possible Gaea
immediately places a worker from her god
card onto a ground-level space
neighboring the dome Gaea starts the
game with two extra workers of her color
on her card when Gaea or an opponent
places a dome if there's at least one or
more unoccupied bronze bases
neighbouring in the gaia player decides
which neighboring ground space to place
the extra worker in this new worker
becomes available for gaia to use on
subsequent turns Gaea can have a maximum
of four workers on the board with so
many extra workers around it won't be
easy to stop one of them from getting to
the top