right god of the waves during our move
each time your worker moves into a
perimeter space it may immediately move
again a quick jaunt in the ocean could
be the advantage you need as long as
your workers move into another parameter
space they can continue to move around
the island the only thing that stops
them is normal move restriction like
only being able to move up one level at
a time and not being able to move on to
a dome you don't always have to take the
extra move so you can end up anywhere
along the coast you want or use a final
move to get back to the middle getting
to where you want is easy when you can
just ride in on the waves