harpies winged menaces on your
opponent's turn each time an opponent's
worker moves this forest space by space
in the same direction until the next
base is a higher level or it is
obstructed the harpies like to harass
your opponent may be hard for them to
move exactly where they want the
opponent has to choose their moves
carefully as any direction they move
will be forced to move continuously in
that direction the only thing that stops
this extra movement is higher level
blocks of the workers domes and the edge
of the board that means an opponent's
worker will only be able to move up if
they started their move
neighboring a block that can move up
onto and unless they're prevented from
moving further end up moving right back
down use the harpies to Menace the
opponent making them flee for safety
away from their goals
you