minotaur bullheaded monster when you
move your worker may move into an
opponent worker space if their worker
can be forced in one space straight
backwards to an unoccupied space at any
level though Minotaur has to follow
rules for moving up or down levels the
forest worker does it so they can be
thrown up the tower Minotaur only
affects opponents so you can't push your
other work out of a space if you get
your own way you cannot push if the
opponent would fall off the island or
have to stand on a dome or another
worker after being forced backwards from
their space when Santorini becomes a
maze feel safe that you'll always have
an exit when you apply a little muscle