[Music]
Urania muse of astronomy on your turn
when your worker moves her builds treat
opposite edges and corners as if they
are adjacent so that every space has
eight neighbors traverse the stars to
arrive at your desired destination when
one of your workers moves off the side
of the board they appear on the opposite
edge of or corner they must still follow
normal move restrictions however so you
couldn't work from a ground-level space
to a level 2 tower but could still win
if warping from a level 2 tower to a
third-level tower because building works
in the same way you can surprise your
opponent by building where it looked
like you could never be able to reach
use the night sky as your roadmap so
you'll never get lost
[Music]