chaos primordial nothingness during
set-up shuffle all unused simple God
powers he dreamed this symbol into a
facedown deck in your play area draw the
top God power and place it face up
beside the deck you have the power of
the face-up god power you must discard
her current god power and draw a new one
after any turn in which at least one
dome is built so you'll still have the
current power for that turn if you were
the one that built the dome if you run
out of God powers shuffle them to create
a new deck and draw the top one when
someone can't decide on who to play a
little chaos gives you a taste of what
the Pantheon offers