Europa and Tallis Queen and Guardian
otamatone cheering set up place the
Tallis token on your god power card at
the end of your turn you may relocate
your Tallis token to any unoccupied
space neighboring the worker that moved
at any time
all players treat the space containing
the Tallis token as if it contains only
a dome let Tallis guard what you
normally can't after moving in building
with one of your Rochas workers they can
summon Tallis to protect themselves for
opponents Tallis cannot be moved to or
built on so is good at getting in your
opponent's way he can be summoned from
anywhere on the island or from your god
card when you need him and he can even
be some into the block you've just built
if you like where he is you can just
have him stay there and guard that space
as well even if your worker moved away
just remember Tallis gets in your way
too so don't leave him somewhere you
need to be as he won't be able to move
until after your workers ever-vigilant
Europa's Guardian will always have her
back while she sits atop her Palace
[Music]