circe divine enchantress at the start of
your turn if an opponent's workers do
not neighbor each other you alone have
the use of their power until your next
turn
Cersei can affect the opponent in two
ways the first limits your opponent's
movement if they'd like to keep the use
of their god power by making sure their
workers are neighbouring each other the
other is to punish them for splitting
their workers apart forcing them to
relinquish their God power at least
until their next turn when they can move
their workers back into neighboring
spaces enchant your opponents away from
each other and take advantage of their
weakness while apart