why a goddess of fate during setup take
the map shield and fate token behind
your shield secretly select a 2x2 square
of fate spaces by placing your fate
token on the map when placing your
workers place three of your collar if an
opponent's worker attempts to win by
moving into one of your fate spaces you
win instead choosing which spaces to
place your fate token on at the start
happens before setting up any workers
and once it's placed can't be moved
so the Marais should try to guide the
opponent to attempt to win in the spaces
they selected but don't be too obvious
you don't want to give your secrets away
boy ray can also win normally by moving
from the second to the third level and
can even do so in two spaces they select
it by the Fate token by playing with the
strings of faith your opponent will
second-guess every chance for glory only
to perhaps have it cut out from under
them
[Music]