silent alluring seeming
during setup place the arrow token
beside the board and oriented in any of
the eight directions to indicate the
direction of the siren song during your
move instead of moving you may force one
or more opponent workers one or two
spaces in the direction of the siren
song two unoccupied spaces of any level
then build with either of your workers
let your song war your opponent to their
defeat after choosing a direction at
setup it now can't be changed for the
rest of the match so make sure your
opponent is clear on which direction
that is just in case the token gets
bumped if an opponent worker would be
forced into a space occupied by a dome
or other worker it cannot be forced
further you can force as many workers as
the opponent has in the direction chosen
at the start but if you give up your
movement you must force at least one of
them one space if your opponent is ready
to set sail to the top of Santorini sing
them an alluring song and scuttle their
plans
[Music]