Hegarty goddess of magic
during set-up take the map shield and to
worker tokens hide the map behind the
shield and secretly place your worker
tokens on the map to represent the
location of your workers on the game
board place role workers last on your
turn
Nouveau worker token on the map as if it
were on the game board build on the game
board as normally at any time if an
opponent attempts an action that would
not be legal due to the presence of your
secret workers their action is canceled
and they lose the rest of their turn
when possible use their power on their
behalf to make their turns legal without
informing them move through the shadows
unseen by your opponent as you move and
build you must still adhere to proper
restrictions because of this it's best
if more experienced players use Hecate
eat so there is no accidental cheating
study your opponent's God as well as it
will be up to Hackett II to use any
powers that affect her workers such as
the Minotaur or Athena getting in your
opponent's way is a good way to prevent
them from taking full turns but be
careful of showing your hand too much or
your secrets will become unraveled
[Music]