[Music]
terpsichore news of dancing on your turn
all of your workers must move and then
all must build your workers move and
build together in a whirlwind
performance both workers must move first
before ID building but do get to move
one after the other if one happens to be
in the other's way then both get to
build once again one after the other
meaning if they are close enough it
could build one block on top of the
other they just built because your
workers must dance this way if either of
them can't move or can't build when they
are supposed to you lose the game as
normal build the city to the beat of the
drum and soon you'll be twirling in the
spotlight