[Music]
nemesis goddess of retribution at the
end of your turn if none of an
opponent's workers neighbor yours you
may force as many of your opponent's
workers as possible to take the spaces
you occupy and vice versa
what was once your enemies will become
yours when drawing on nemesis is power
because her ability comes at the end of
the turn you'll have plenty of
opportunity to set up for it
just make sure that neither of your
workers are neighboring one of theirs
when you do an actual retribution you
must swap both of your workers with
fairs for good or bad you can't pick
only one pair of workers to swap it must
be both if your opponent has an
advantage put yourself at a disadvantage
and then take it all away from them
retribution is a dish best served from
the top of Santorini
[Music]