Aeolus god of desire during setup place
your workers anywhere along opposite
edges of the board you also win if one
of your workers moves to a space
neighboring your other worker and both
are on the first level for the same
level in a three-player game it's a tale
of lovers meeting in the middle who your
workers can meet anywhere on the first
level and win one block is all it takes
to prevent your else's win sometimes so
make sure to leave a lot of meat up
opportunity by building level one blocks
towards your other worker and anything
higher out of the way and don't forget
you can still win normally so a long
distance relationship isn't the end of
the world for eros love conquers all
which is going to make it hard for your
opponent to keep the couple apart
[Music]