[Music]
Zeus god of the sky during your build
your worker may build a block under
itself as the ruler of Mount Olympus
Zeus knows how to get to the pinnacle
his workers know to and can make sure
they're never stuck lower than they want
to be any move can become a way up when
you can build on yourself so it'll be
hard for your opponent to block you by
building too high just remember that the
workers must move first before building
under themselves so it can still get
stuck if they can't move to win you must
move from the second level to the third
so building yourself up to the third
level doesn't remember the game the
skies are yours so take your place among
the heavens as often as you like
[Music]