Gaea goddess of the earth when a worker
builds a dome Gaea may immediately place
a worker from her god called on to a
ground-level space
neighboring the dome Gaea starts the
game with two extra workers of her color
on her card when Gaia or an opponent
places a dome if there's at least one or
more unoccupied ground spaces
neighboring it the Gaea player decides
which neighbor and ground space to place
the extra worker in this new worker
becomes available for Gaea to use on
subsequent turns Gaia can have a maximum
of four workers on the board for so many
extra workers around it won't be easy to
stop one of them from getting to the top