deep in the heart of the Aegean Sea a
long time ago before you and me when the
gods of the Pantheon did not yet have
fame they met in the ocean and invented
the game
the top Mount Olympus you sat on his
throne
and none of his children
so he commanded the teens in a
thunderous toad the immortal kids go
outside and leave me alone
but Zeus was unaware of what he implored
as mr. vis a product of a God who is
bored
ere is seen lot of hues to regard him as
Lord and since Spartan and Trojan to die
by the soul water until on the horizon
he eventually spied an extremely tall
island that was not very wide some
pathetic humans are building a village
was a great opportunity to go over and
pillage
but Aphrodite stopped him and decided to
ask why must you always make destruction
your task instead let us help them build
this wonderful city destroying those
domes would be a terrible pity you guide
them your way
I'll guide the mine so we can both help
them finish these temples divine when
one of our towers rises above all the
rest we shall see you can help these
humans better than the best so they
constructed quite quickly using builders
to claim the highest point on the island
for their own God
each of the guards have their own
special powers they use to their
advantage while erecting their towers
upon realizing at a point
could be predicted these gods couldn't
help it they were completely addicted
there he said what fun let us give this
a name
you smoke from above we shall call it a
game so they've in century
by shaping the force of those women
and each time they built it it was never
the same
he's had to smash it
zoos really so the kids for the best bad
son
they no longer stared at the boobs just
getting done
so next time you wonder which game came
before
century
since its inception over 30 years ago
Santorini has been continuously enhanced
and refined by mathematician and
educator dr. Gordon Hamilton Santorini
is a highly accessible pure strategy
game it is simple enough for an
elementary school classroom but with
enough gameplay depth and content for
even hardcore gamers to explore
Santorini is truly a game for everyone
the rules are deceptively simple each
turn move one of your builders into a
neighboring space then construct a
building level adjacent to the door be
removed you may step up a maximum of one
level or step down any number of levels
when building on top of the third level
place it to him instead removing that
space from play if either of your
builders reaches the third level you win
Santorini features 68 highly detailed
building miniatures for building
miniatures and a custom-designed
elevated iron play surface creating the
beautiful 3d tabletop experience but
what makes Santorini truly special is
its seamless integration of variable
player panels into a pure strategy game
dr. Hamilton is designed over 40
thematic garden hero powers each
fundamentally changing the way the game
is played your contribution to the
project will help unlock various stretch
goals further improving the component
quality of the game we will also be
unlocking a pantheon of new god and hero
powers each adding significant replay
value by potentially creating over 1,000
interesting and unique confrontations
Santorini
learned in 30 seconds play it for life
[Music]