the Golden Fleece a 2-player expansion
for Santorini the Golden Fleece confers
the blessing of the gods to the
villagers of Santorini when sitting up
instead of each player choosing a God
select a God that will be represented by
the Golden Fleece and place the card in
the center of the table beside the board
players then set up their builders as
normal the player who placed first then
places the Golden Fleece in any free
space and the other player takes the
first term the Eddy builder starts their
turn neighboring the Golden Fleece both
of that players builders are imbued with
the power of the God until the start of
their next turn four gods whose power
only affects opponents such as Hades if
at the start of your turn the opponent's
builder is neighboring the Golden Fleece
then you are affected by the gods power
of the back turn the Golden Fleece
expansion for Santorini changing the way
you build to the stars